http://toothfairy.org/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
You Are HereHomePrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which ToothFairy.org collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the www.ToothFairy.org website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by ToothFairy.org.
Personal identification
information
We may collect personal
identification information from Users in a variety of ways in connection with
activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site..
Users may visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information
from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can
always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it
may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-personal identification
information
We may collect non-personal
identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site.
Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type
of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our
Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized
and other similar information.
Web browser cookies
Our Site may use “cookies” to
enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive
for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User
may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when
cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not
function properly.
How we use collected information
ToothFairy.org may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:
To improve customer service Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently. To personalize user experience We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site. To improve our Site We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services. To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them. To send periodic emails If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data
collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect
against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your
personal information, username, password, transaction information and data
stored on our Site.
Sharing your personal information
We do not sell, trade, or rent
Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic
aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification
information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted
affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.
Third party websites
Users may find advertising or
other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners,
suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not
control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible
for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition,
these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly
changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and
customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website,
including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s
own terms and policies.
Advertising
Ads appearing on our site may
be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These
cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you
an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information
about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks
to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will
be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of
cookies by any advertisers.
Google Adsense
Some of the ads may be served
by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based
on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non
personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information
about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt
out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network
privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html
Changes to this privacy policy
ToothFairy.org
has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we
will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to
frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are
helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and
agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically
and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify
your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do
not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of
changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site,
please contact us
Most Recent
When baby teeth fall out?
What happen if you don’t brush your teeths?
What are the most common dental problems ?
What are the early signs of dental trouble?
What are the best ways to practice good oral hygiene at home ?
Should kids use mouthwash regularly for caring teeths
How often should kids get a dental checkup
HOW KEEPING YOU’RE CHILDS TEETH HEALTHY
How do kids prevent tooth decay, gingivitis and other problems?
10 tips to look after your teeth and keep safe
